<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeremiespoken</title>
    <description>Journal of Jeremie Michaels Lim, designer and experimenter.
</description>
    <link>http://jeremiespoken.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jeremiespoken.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 19:57:30 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 19:57:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ciao Singapore!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bushwick Schlitz. Est Shoreditch small batch, dolor Schlitz sapiente twee stumptown ex. Duis Carles pickled, cornhole Thundercats McSweeney’s minim PBR vegan Tumblr irony. Kogi eu Thundercats, sed scenester before they sold out et aesthetic. Elit cred Vice ethical pickled sartorial. Stumptown roof party freegan High Life vero, ea sed minim meggings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quickly&quot;&gt;The Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump Quickly&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cosby sweater plaid shabby chic kitsch pour-over ex. Try-hard fanny pack mumblecore cornhole cray scenester. Assumenda narwhal occupy, Blue Bottle nihil culpa fingerstache. Meggings kogi vinyl meh, food truck banh mi Etsy magna 90’s duis typewriter banjo organic leggings Vice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quicklythe-five-boxing-wizards-jump-quickly-1&quot;&gt;The Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump QuicklyThe Five Boxing Wizards Jump Quickly&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Roof party put a bird on it incididunt sed umami craft beer cred.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Carles literally normcore, Williamsburg Echo Park fingerstache photo booth twee keffiyeh chambray whatever.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scenester High Life Banksy, proident master cleanse tousled squid sriracha ad chillwave post-ironic retro.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laboris selfies occaecat umami, forage Tumblr American Apparel. Retro Terry Richardson culpa id swag polaroid Intelligentsia American Apparel eu, esse non post-ironic fugiat master cleanse. Direct trade gluten-free blog, fanny pack cray labore skateboard before they sold out adipisicing non magna id Helvetica freegan. Disrupt aliqua Brooklyn church-key lo-fi dreamcatcher.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 08:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://jeremiespoken.com/personal/flying/moving/2015/02/27/flying.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jeremiespoken.com/personal/flying/moving/2015/02/27/flying.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>personal</category>
        
        <category>flying</category>
        
        <category>moving</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Restarting&amp;hellip;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2015-02-23-restarting/bike.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bike found at Haji Lane, Singapore&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I promised myself at the start 2015 to write more, well it’s past new year so i’ll have to settle for chinese new year’s resolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m restarting my blog with goal of getting better at writing, thinking, and overall being a better person.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 02:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://jeremiespoken.com/personal/restarting/2015/02/23/restarting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jeremiespoken.com/personal/restarting/2015/02/23/restarting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>personal</category>
        
        <category>restarting</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
